A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Information Services, RG 11 FA1360
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation records, Information Services, RG 11
1913-1989
1968-1982
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation
FA1360
2.37 Cubic Feet 5 letter document boxes and 1 legal document box.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Arrangement
Original order, as received.
Scope and Contents
The Rockefeller Foundation Information Services records are comprised of select program reports and special studies, news clippings, staff memos and notes, manuals and directories.
- The Rockefeller Foundation's Equal Opportunity Program: A Short History, Elizabeth Romney, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
- Typical Charity Organizations and their Ways of Raising Money, 1921 November 21 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Information on Community Chests, 1922 May 26 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Kinsey Report on Sex Research - Lawer File, 1953-1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Program and Policy Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Arts and Humanities Clippings - Dance, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Arts and Humanities Clippings - Film and Television, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Arts and Humanities Clippings - Music, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
- Arts and Humanities Clippings - Other Areas, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Arts and Humanities Clippings - Theatre, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Arts and Humanities Clippings - Writing, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Program Committee News Clippings, 1979-1981 (Box 2, Folder 8-10)
- Activities List, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 1-3)
  Scope and Contents
  For Board of Directors and Executive Committee meetings.
- Weekly Activities List, 1972-1982 (Box 3, Folder 4-13)
- PAX Lists, 1961-1982 (Box 4, Folder 1-11)
  Staff name and professional contact information (office phone).
- Directory of New York Staff, 1950-1959; 1961-1966; 1969-1972; 1974 (Box 6, Folder 12-18)
- Directory of New York Staff, 1975-1985, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 12-19)
- Directory of Officers and Staff, 1960; 1961; 1963; 1965; 1967; 1968; 1970; 1971; 1973 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Directory of Field Staff and Personnel on Special Assignment, 1969; 1972-1974; 1976-1979; 1981-1984 (Box 6, Folder 4-11)
- Staff Manual, 1952; 1972 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Fellows Manual, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Memos to All Staff - General, 1964; 1969-1982 (Box 5, Folder 1-11)
- Memos to All Staff - Arts Program, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Memos to Officers, Department Heads, Program Associates, 1972-1975 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Staff Notices, 1969-1981 (Box 5, Folder 14-22)
- Rockefeller Foundation Trustees, 1913-1987 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  Includes term of service.
- Personnel, 1936 (Box 6, Folder 2)